bd.gov.hk 2019-10-19

# Privacy Policy Statement - Buildings Department

You are welcome to browse the information of this Buildings Department (BD) Web site.

The contents of this site have been developed in accordance with the provisions of the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (PDPO). The PDPO provides data subjects with rights to ascertain whether BD holds personal data relating to them, to access to that data, and to correct any data that is inaccurate. Such requests should be made in the [Data Access Request Form (No.OPS003 issued by the Privacy Commissioner)](http://www.pcpd.org.hk/english/publications/files/Dforme.pdf "New window to: Data Access Request Form \(No.OPS003 issued by the Privacy Commissioner\)") and sent to us by mail to the Data Controlling Officer, G/F, Buildings Department Headquarters, North Tower, West Kowloon Government Offices, 11 Hoi Ting Road, Yau Ma Tei, Kowloon. By virtue of Section 20(3)(e) of the PDPO, a data access request may be refused if it is not made in this Form.

Site visitors can freely explore this site without having to reveal any personal data. The HKSAR Government will however make a record of IP address and/or domain name, and the pages visited for each hit. It does not collect any personally identifiable information from the visitors. The recorded information will only be used to generate summarized visitor statistics.

In addition, BD is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites to which we are linked.

If you have any enquiries about the above, please e-mail them to us.

* * *
